videodeck.net 2015-06-10

# Video Deck for YouTube™

Privacy Policy

COMCODE d.o.o., as the owner of this website, created this privacy statement to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy of our visitors and customers. As a company, we strictly adhere to all industry guidelines and we continually review our policy and procedures to ensure the safety and protection of our customer information. There follows an explanation of our commitment to protecting the privacy of Internet Users. 

Information Collection and Use 

COMCODE d.o.o. is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from those which are disclosed in this statement. COMCODE d.o.o. collects information from our users at several different points on our website. 

Cookies 

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the users hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. 

Cookies on our site 

We use Google Analytics (just like virtually everybody else) a service provided by Google. They gather anonymous data of how people are using this site and then provide us with visitor statistics, details of page views etc etc. If you are anti-Google you can opt-out of being tracked by Google Analytics at <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout> (we’d prefer you didn’t though as this data is seriously helpful to us in improving our website and to provide a better experience for you!) The cookies which Google places on your computer are called: _utma, _utmb, _utmc and _utmz. Click [here](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) for an overview of privacy at Google. 

This is a list of basic information about cookies used on our site: 

#### Cookie Name

| 

#### Duration the cookie is on your computer

| 

#### When Can I delete the cookie myself?  
  
---|---|---  
_utma | 2 years | Whenever you like!  
_utmb | Less than 1 Day | Whenever you like!  
_utmc | Deletes itself when you leave our website | Whenever you like!  
_utmz | 6 Months | Whenever you like!  
Session | Deletes itself when you leave our website | Whenever you like!  
PersistentCookie | 1 Year | Whenever you like!  
  
If you don't like cookies you can get instructions for deletion [here](http://www.wikihow.com/Clear-Your-Browser's-Cookies). 

Log files 

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track site use, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

Links 

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we Comcode d.o.o. are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

Security 

This website takes every precaution to protect our users information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, the information is protected both online and off-line. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our user information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information.
